[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "Which number is written in standard form for <br>400 + 20 + 5?",
    "options": [
      "425",
      "452",
      "405",
      "524"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "What is the standard form of <br>300 + 60 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "639",
      "396",
      "369",
      "963"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "What is the standard form of <br>200 + 50 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "251",
      "521",
      "215",
      "152"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "Which number represents <br>700 + 30 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "378",
      "783",
      "807",
      "738"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "What is 500 + 40 + 3 in standard form?",
    "options": [
      "453",
      "534",
      "543",
      "354"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "What is the expanded form of 684?",
    "options": [
      "600 + 80 + 4",
      "680 + 4",
      "600 + 8 + 40",
      "60 + 800 + 4"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "Write 407 in expanded form:",
    "options": [
      "400 + 70 + 7",
      "400 + 7",
      "40 + 7",
      "400 + 0 + 7"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "Which of the following is the expanded form of 532?",
    "options": [
      "530 + 2",
      "530 + 30 + 2",
      "500 + 3 + 20",
      "50 + 320"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "What is the expanded form of 720?",
    "options": [
      "700 + 20",
      "700 + 2",
      "700 + 20 + 0",
      "70 + 20 + 0"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "What is 356 in expanded form?",
    "options": [
      "300 + 5 + 60",
      "350 + 6",
      "300 + 50 + 6",
      "30 + 56"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  }
]
